Hi, and that's why some years ago learn how to find better answers with Chagivity using
web storage and deep research.
Sometimes you need information that goes beyond Chagivity building knowledge.
Maybe you're exploring a new library or checking just breaking changes or trying to fix
some error that it's not in the training data yet.
That exactly wins as two features become incredibly powerful for you.
Let's start with the web search.
So the web search feature lets Chagivity browse the internet in real time, finds the most
recent and relevant information for you.
One is enabled you will see a small compost icon at the top of your chart.
So when you click on plus icon you can enable the click more and click web search.
You will see the web search is enabled.
On this active Chagivity can read official documentation, some GitHub issues on the web
sites, some change works, release notes, or some for example trusted blog posts or other
websites.
Usually web search is quick.
It takes about 5-10 seconds depending on how complex information you want to find.
So let's practice.
So let's ask something, for example imagine we have an existing application and they want
to ask how to install some libraries in this.
So I will ask the search how to install by a wind library in nice, gorgeous application.
You see it search and the web and it's really fast it take you seconds and then it will
respond to you this information.
So you see here provide your steps how to install it.
So you first need to install the library or you can also configure files, so you see the
detailed response which you can follow up and if you scroll down you might found some
resources.
For example if you see the sentence and Chagivity take it from one website you see the
resources right here you can switch between them.
So you see it's to information from official how wind and niches web sites.
For example here he search information at the stack overflow and you can click on it and
you will be redirected to this web page.
So also below so you have sources.
If you click on this sources you'll see all the sources where Chagivity did the search.
So you see it's quite a big number of sources.
And you can go one by one if you're interested to learn it deeper.
So you can also ask Chagivity to try again if you don't like the answer but I recommend
you if you don't like the search results just write the prompt word actually you don't
like.
Because you just click try again Chagivity don't know what you don't like and do make can
do some mistakes you don't really want.
So let's do it quickly another example like how we can install the database as a super
base you see it takes a bit longer like we like it and Chagivity asking our opinion.
So which type of response we prefer more like his also a plane and trying to find a better
answer for us.
I'll prefer more the second one I'm going to choose it quickly but as you see it also
provide some basic steps with detailed instructions so you can use this feature if you
want to find something in the commentation okay he's finished or not I don't understand
no he's not finished okay I prefer this response and it's right here but you can switch
between the type of responses okay let's not talk about deep research so no maybe let's
talk first when web search feature is useful for you so when you want to learn how to configure
or the top new library like we did we need to check for example some recent syntax changes
update in new library or when you want to get an explanation of some error message you
don't understand but beyond the Chagivity normally do the search sometimes automatically
but if you want to especially if you did web search for your request you can enable it
manually so and for example web search is useful when you don't want to spend 10, 15 minutes
in Google finding different transfers search and transfers over Stack Overflow, GitHub
features and set up Chagivity can do it for you so we use it now we talk about deep research
deep research going even further while web search just find some quick transfers deep research
performs as the full investigation assistant across multiple sources so we can see and
think of it like developer assistant doing structured research for you it will collect
some data it will analyze information it will give some clear conclusion and usually
deep research might take 5, 10 minutes depending on how complex is your question sometimes
it can take 15 minutes if you ask really complex questions but you can just switch to work
you doing and then back in 10 minutes to your deep research chat and see okay given the time
chagivity view reviews different websites will compare different solutions and write a clear
summary with prompts and cons and examples for you and also at the end they'll give you
some summary okay what you should do let's try to do the deep research you mentioned
I am breaking direct project and I want to compare the eight management tools where I store
my data and I will just disable the search and you click plus and use the deep research
as you see you have some limitations on the pre account but so you can use it okay I
will start the deep research you see now chagivity will ask me some additional questions normally
you do it because you want to prepare the better research for me yeah okay he's asking
I a primary user react with functional components and hooks so I can answer yes the second
one do a plan to manage global stage or does many components or most local components
state let's say global so gonna share my data between a lot of components I work on small project
large apps of both let's say most let's say small apps just to limit the response do
prepare tools with me no set up minimal okay let's you see he understands our answer and he
start on the deep research so if you don't want to wait I already did same deep research
previously and I just will show you the results so let's scroll where is the deep research
yeah you see I also have same question it asked me a bit different information but let's see
here see how much time he spent on deep research how much sources he searched and how much
sources and sources he did so you will see as it also he do some intramassage explaining about
the state management we ask then he try compare everything one by one so first we start with
react context API he did an overview and provide some usage examples so you will understand
and also he will explain different points like log and corov integrations let's give the port
use case stability and etc etc etc etc is the next one is zustan we same have an intro we have
example of code usage and here are same and we have same bullet points so it's really easy for
comparison and also you see the sources both specific sentences where you find this information
so you can also visit this website and see okay and then we have react toolkit we have same
example the same bullet points and below you have the comparison table so you can compare all
the three tools by each is the point and it's really useful and next we have summary oh what we see
we see complexity is the simplest one but basically global state more extra libraries it's fine
so zustan is lightweight and very easy to learn okay it's fine it has to less boiler plate
and reduction keep is as the highest initial cause and learning and setup but it's good for large
and complex application so you can see the summary and it will help you better understand the
what library should use so one deep research is ideal for it's ideal for technical decisions
that require some comparing options as you see in this table of course it is stable if you need to
do some architecture research like choosing technologies database is building tools libraries etc
when exploring new AI or JavaScript framework or any other framework for other languages so
that change fast you can also run deeper search if summarize a lesson if you need quick facts
you can use web search if you need to make a complex decision or want to have a deep analysis
always use a deep search you can even combine them you can start just with asking a question
if you don't like that just a simple answer without web search you can ask a gpt to search
at the internet to get more quick insights and if you send it's not enough you can always ask
for deep research and get more detailed breakdown okay hope this lesson was useful for you
and see you in the next lessons